Sinclair Browning Papers, 1942-2009 (bulk 1997-2000)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Sinclair Browning Papers, 1942-2009 bulk (1997-2000)
MS 535
Browning, Sinclair
Sinclair Browning Papers, 1942-2009 (bulk 1997-2000) is comprised of the personal and professional papers of Southern Arizona author Sinclair Browning. The bulk of the material relates to the first five books of the Trade Ellis mystery series, published 1999-2003. The remaining material relates to several self-published novels and unpublished material. Items included in this collection are correspondence, research materials including news clippings and interviews, manuscript drafts, screenplays, and cover art.
8 Linear Feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
There are no restrictions on this collection.
Biographical Note
Zerilda Sinclair Browning (b. November 17, 1946) is a Southwestern mystery writer and self-ascribed “dirty-shirt” cowgirl. A native of California, she moved to Southern Arizona as a child and grew up on a family cattle ranch. She has spent the majority of her life as a cattle rancher and team penner. Before writing the Trade Ellis series, she co-authored Lyons on Horses(Doubleday, 1991) with horse trainer John Lyons. In 1999, she published the first Trade Ellis mystery, The Last Song Dogs. Her stories feature Trade Ellis, a part-Apache private investigator and rancher. Browning is known for her vivid descriptions of Southwestern culture and landscapes as well as her use of real-life murders as foundations for her plots. Her books have been nominated for both the Shamus and Barry awards, and she was a nominee for the Arizona Arts Award. She currently lives in Northern Arizona.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into 12 series
Series I:The Last Song Dogs, 1989-2000
Subseries 1: Research, 1989-2000
Subseries 2: Correspondence, 1992-1999
Subseries 3: Publicity, 1993-2000
Subseries 4: Manuscript, 1998-2001
Series II:The Sporting Club, 1993-2001
Subseries 1: Research, 1997-2000
Subseries 2: Correspondonce, 1994-2001
Subseries 3: Publicity, 1994-2000
Subseries 4: Manuscript, 1997-2000
Series III:Rode Hard, Put Away Dead, 1997-2002
Subseries 1: Research, 1997-2000
Subseries 2: Correspondence, 1999-2001
Subseries 3: Publicity, 2000-2002
Subseries 4: Manuscript, 2000-2001
Series IV: Crack Shot, 1994-2003
Subseries 1: Research, 1994-2001
Subseries 2: Correspondence, 2000-2002
Subseries 3: Publicity, 2001
Subseries 4: Manuscript, 2001-2003
Series V: Traggedy Ann, 1997-2003
Subseries 1: Research, 1997-2002
Subseries 2: Correspondence, 2000-2003
Subseries 3: Publicity, 2003
Subseries 4: Manuscript, 2001-2003
Series VI:America's Best, 1942-2001
Subseries 1: Research, 1942-2001
Subseries 2: Correspondence, 1990-1995
Subseries 3: Publicity, 1995
Subseries 4: Manuscript, undated
Series VII: Feathers Brush My Heart 2000-2009
Subseries 1: Correspondence, 2000-2009
Subseries 2: Publicity, 2001
Series VIII:Bobby Bad, 2002-2010
Subseries 1: Research, 2002-2003
Subseries 2: Manuscript, 2005-2010
Series IX:Standard Messiah, 2001
Subseries 1: Manuscript, 2001
Series X:Harvesting Ray, 2004-2005
Subseries 1: Research, 2004-2005
Subseries 2: Manuscript, 2004
Series XI: Feathers Brush My Heart 2, 1990-2013
Subseries 1: Research, 2002
Subseries 2: Correspondence, 1998-2013
Series XII:Other Writings, 1968-2003
Subseries 1: Classes Taught, undated
Subseries 2: Fiction, 1988-2000
Subseries 3: Non Fiction, 1968-2003
Subseries 4: Poetry, undated
Subseries 5: Screenplays, 1980-2003
Subseries 6: Speeches, 2003
Scope and Content Note
Papers 1942-2009 (bulk 1997-2000): This collection consists of the personal and professional papers of Sinclair Browning. The bulk of the material consists of the materials used and generated for the writing of the Trade Ellis mystery series, specifically The Last Song Dogs; The Sporting Club; Rode Hard, Put Away Dead; Crack Shot; and Traggedy Ann. The remaining material relates to several self-published novels, unpublished screenplays, and various nonfiction articles. The materials include newspaper and magazine clippings about current events, interviews with professionals, correspondence from both editors and fans, and varied manuscript drafts. There are also publicity materials including notices for book signing events, book reviews, and advertisements.
Access Terms
Browning, Sinclair.
Women private investigators.
Women novelists -- Arizona -- Fiction.
Women ranchers -- Arizona.
Arizona -- Fiction.
Arizona -- Non Fiction.
Tucson (Ariz.).
Mystery and detective stories.
American literature -- Southwestern States.
Container List
- Series 1: The Last Song Dogs, 1989-2000
  This series contains the material pertaining to the creation and publication of The Last Song Dogs. The material is organized by the timeline in which the information was created and used, from conception to final edits.
  - Subseries 1: Research, 1989-2000
    This subseries contains the news articles and plot notes used to write The Last Song Dogs. It also contains a list of possible publishers for the Trade Ellis series.
    - Chapter Breakdowns, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - News Articles, 1989-1999, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Plot Notes, 1993,1997, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Possible Publishers, 1993-2000, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 2: Correspondence, 1992-1999
    This subseries contains correspondence between Browning and the editors at Bantam. Also included are fan mail and queries, or the letters requesting an agent or publisher to consider a manuscript for representation or publication, respectively.
    - Bantam, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Blurb Requests, 1997-1999, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Crawford, Susan, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Editors, 1997-1999, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Fan Mail, 1999, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Gerecke, Jeff, 1996-1997, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Powers, Amanda Clay, 1997-1998, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Queries, 1992-1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 3: Publicity, 1993-2000
    This subseries contains material related to the marketing of The Last Song Dogs, including book reviews, mockups of the jacket cover, and flyers promoting book signing events.
    - Book Cover, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Book Reviews (Folder 1 of 2), 1999-2000, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Book Reviews (Folder 2 of 2), 1999-2000, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Public Relations, 1993-2000, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Synopsis, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 4: Manuscripts, 1998-2001
    This subseries contains drafts of the manuscript for The Last Song Dogs, including a rewrite that contains line by line edits.
    - Line Edited 2nd Rewrite (Folder 1 of 2), January 1998 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Line Edited 2nd Rewrite (Folder 2 of 2), January 1998 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Original Manuscript (Folder 1 of 2), 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Original Manuscript (Folder 2 of 2), 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Series 2: The Sporting Club, 1993-2001
  This series contains material pertaining to the creation and publication of The Sporting Club. The material is organized by the timeline in which the information was created and used, from conception to final edits.
  - Subseries 1: Research, 1993-1999
    This subseries contains news articles, book excerpts, and printed timelines concerning the civil rights movement and racist groups; also included are Browning’s notes on the plot.
    - Ku Klux Klan Information, 1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - News Articles, 1993-1999, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Plot Notes, 1993, 1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Timelines, circa 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 2: Correspondence, 1994-2001
    This subseries contains emails and letters between Browning, her editing team, and her fans.
    - Editors, 1994, 1998-2000, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Fan Mail (Folder 1 of 2), 2000-2001, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Fan Mail (Folder 2 of 2), 2000-2001, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 3: Publicity, 1994-2001
    This subseries contains material for the marketing of The Sporting Club, including book reviews, interviews with Browning, and mockups of the book jacket.
    - Book Cover, 1999, 2000, circa 1999 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Book Reviews, 1999-2001, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Marketing Materials, 1994-2000, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Synopsis, circa 1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 4: Manuscript, 1997-2000
    This subseries contains manuscript drafts of The Sporting Club, including a digital composition of the book, or the mockup of what the manuscript will look like once published.
    - Revised Manuscript (Folder 1 of 3), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Revised Manuscript (Folder 2 of 3), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Revised Manuscript (Folder 3 of 3), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Rewrite Notes, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Uncorrected Proofs, circa 1999 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Digital Composition, 14 October 1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Original Manuscript (Folder 1 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Original Manuscript (Folder 2 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Series 3: Rode Hard, Put Away Dead, 1997-2002
  This series contains material pertaining to the creation and publication of Rode Hard, Put Away Dead. The material is organized by the timeline in which the information was created and used, from conception to final edits.
  - Subseries 1: Research, 1997-2000
    This subseries contains news articles concerning the murder that Rode Hard, Put Away Dead is based on, as well as Browning’s notes on plot and characters.
    - Character Development, 1997-2000, circa 1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Margaret Lesher, 1997-1998, 2001, circa 2001 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - News Articles, 1998-2000, circa 1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Plot Notes, 1998-1999, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 2: Correspondence, 1999-2001
    This subseries contains email and letter correspondence between Browning, her editing team, and her fans.
    - Editors, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Fan Mail, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 3: Publicity, 2000-2002
    This subseries contains the marketing materials for Rode Hard, Put Away Dead, including book reviews, mockups of the jacket cover, and flyers for book signing events.
    - Book Reviews, 2001, circa 2001 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Cover, 2000, circa 2000 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Public Relations, 2000-2002, circa 2000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 4: Manuscript, 2000-2001
    This subseries contains manuscript drafts of Rode Hard, Put Away Dead, including a digital composition, or mockup of what the manuscript will look like once published.
    - Digital Composition, 09 November 2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Edited Manuscript (Folder 1 of 3), 2001 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Edited Manuscript (Folder 2 of 3), 2001 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Edited Manuscript (Folder 3 of 3), 2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Uncorrected Page Proofs, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Series 4: Crack Shot, 1994-2003
  This series contains material pertaining to the creation and publication of Crack Shot, also referred to as Fast Eddy. The material is organized by the timeline in which the information was created and used, from conception to final edits.
  - Subseries 1: Research, 1994-2001
    This subseries contains news articles on the reformatory boys’ camps that were an inspiration for Crack Shot, as well as Browning’s notes on plot.
    - Desert Hills Articles, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Disciplinary Camps News Articles, 1998-2001, circa 1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - News Articles, 1994, 1998-2000, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Plot Notes, 1998-2001, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Subseries 2: Correspondence, 2000-2002
    This subseries contains emails and letters between Browning and her editing team.
    - Editors, 2000-2001, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Subseries 3: Publicity, 2001
    This subseries contains marketing materials for Crack Shot, including mockups of the jacket cover and book reviews.
    - Cover, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Reviews, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 4: Manuscript, 2001-2003
    This subseries contains drafts of the manuscript, including a digital composition of Crack Shot, or the mockup of what the manuscript will look like once published.
    - Digital Composition (Folder 1 of 2), 2001 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Digital Composition (Folder 2 of 2), 2001 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Rewrite, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Uncorrected Page Proof, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Edited Manuscript (Folder 1 of 3), 2002 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Edited Manuscript (Folder 2 of 3), 2002 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Edited Manuscript (Folder 3 of 3), 2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - First Draft (Folder 1 of 2), 2003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - First Draft (Folder 2 of 2), 2003 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Final Draft (Folder 1 of 2), 2003 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Final Draft (Folder 2 of 2), 2003 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Series 5: Traggedy Ann, 1997-2003
  This series contains material pertaining to the creation and publication of Traggedy Ann. The material is organized by the timeline in which the information was created and used, from conception to final edits.
  - Subseries 1: Research, 1997-2002
    This subseries contains news clippings concerning the murder that Traggedy Ann was based on, as well as Browning’s notes on character and plot. Also included are photos of “Tragedy Ann,” the gothic-themed doll that the title comes from.
    - Amy Andrews Murder, 1997, 2001, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Character Development, 1998, 2001, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - News Articles & Transcripts, 1997, 2000-2001, circa 1997 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Occult Research, 1999-2001, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Plot Notes, 2001-2002, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Tragedy Ann, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 2: Correspondence, 2000-2003
    This subseries contains emails and letters between Browning, her editing team, and her fans. Also included are letters of permission that Browning received from people who had won a chance to have their name included within Traggedy Ann.
    - Editors, 2000-2003 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Fan Mail (Folder 1 of 2), 2000-2003, circa 2002 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Fan Mail (Folder 2 of 2), 2000-2003, circa 2002 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Permission Letters, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 3: Publicity, 2003
    This subseries contains the mockup book jacket used for the distribution of Traggedy Ann.
    - Cover, 2003, circa 2003 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 4: Manuscript, 2001-2002
    This subseries contains varied manuscript drafts of Traggedy Ann, including the first pass page proofs, or a copy of the manuscript with the initial editing notes.
    - Edited Manuscript (Folder 1 of 4), circa 2001 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Edited Manuscript (Folder 2 of 4), circa 2001 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Edited Manuscript (Folder 3 of 4), circa 2001 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Edited Manuscript (Folder 4 of 4), circa 2001 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Rewrite, 2002, circa 2002 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - First Pass Page Proofs (Folder 1 of 3), 21 May 2003 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - First Pass Page Proofs (Folder 2 of 3), 21 May 2003 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - First Pass Page Proofs (Folder 3 of 3), 21 May 2003 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Series 6: America's Best, 1942-2001
  This series contains material pertaining to the creation and publication of America’s Best. The material is organized by the timeline in which the information was created and used, from research to publication. This novel is the first to be published outside of the Trade Ellis series.
  - Subseries 1: Research, 1942-2001
    This subseries contains the research by Browning in the creation of America’s Best. Included are letters from actual survivors of the Arisan Maru, and the official accounts of what occurred the day the ship sank.
    - Arisan Maru, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Calvin Graef Transcript, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Freedom of Information Act Request, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Life Articles, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Mike's Letters from Cabanatuan, 1942-1944 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Pitches, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Santo Tomas Internment Camp, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 2: Correspondence, 1990-1995
    This subseries contains correspondence from survivors of the Arisan Maru concerning America’s Best.
    - Childress, Clyde, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Survivor Letters, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 3: Publicity, 1995
    This subseries contains the published book reviews for America’s Best.
    - Book Reviews, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 4: Manuscript, undated
    This subseries contains the unpublished screenplay of America’s Best.
    - Screenplay, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Series 7: Feathers Brush My Heart, 2000-2009
  This series contains the materials pertaining to the creation of Feathers Brush My Heart. This includes correspondence from fans of the book and book reviews.
  - Subseries 1: Correspondence, 2000-2009
    This subseries contains the letters sent to Browning from people who wanted to express their enjoyment of the book. In addition, there are letters from Browning’s personal friend and fellow author, Bill Brooks.
    - Brooks, Bill, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Fan Mail (Folder 1 of 4), 2000-2009 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Fan Mail (Folder 2 of 4), 2000-2009 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Fan Mail (Folder 3 of 4), 2000-2009 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Fan Mail, 2000-2009 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 2: Publicity, 2001
    This subseries contains book reviews published concerning eathers Brush My Heart.
    - Book Reviews, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Series 8: Bobby Bad, 2002-2010
  This series contains material pertaining to the creation and publication of Bobby Bad. The material is organized by the timeline in which the information was created and used, from research to publication. This novel was self-published by Browning as an e-book.
  - Subseries 1: Research, 2002-2003
    This subseries contains the research and plot notes that Browning used to create Bobby Bad.
    - Chapter Breakdowns, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Research, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Plot Notes, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 2: Manuscript, 2005-2010
    This subseries contains both the original and the edited manuscripts of Bobby Bad.
    - Edited Manuscript (Folder 1 of 3), circa 2005 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Edited Manuscript (Folder 2 of 3), circa 2005 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Edited Manuscript (Folder 3 of 3), circa 2005 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Original Manuscript (Folder 1 of 2), circa 2010 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Original Manuscript (Folder 2 of 2), circa 2010 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Series 9: Standard Messiah, 2001
  This series contains the manuscript and screenplay of Browning’s novel Standard Messiah. This novel was self-published by Browning as an e-book.
  - Subseries 1: Manuscript, 2001
    This subseries contains the original manuscript of Standard Messiah, as well as the unpublished screenplay.
    - Original Manuscript (Folder 1 of 2), undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Original Manuscript (Folder 2 of 2), undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Screenplay, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Series 10: Harvesting Ray, 2004-2005
  This series contains material used by Browning to create the novel Harvesting Ray, including research and the edited manuscript. Browning self-published this novel as an e-book.
  - Subseries 1: Research, 2004-2005
    This series contains the research used to create Harvesting Ray, including articles on organ donation and cellular memory.
    - Bad Organs, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Brain Death, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Cellular Memory, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Chapter Breakdowns, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Heart Donors, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Heart Transplant, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Research, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Plot Notes, circa 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Subseries 2: Manuscript, 2004
    This subseries contains the edited manuscript of Harvesting Ray.
    - Edited Manuscript (Folder 1 of 3), 8 October 2004 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Edited Manuscript (Folder 2 of 3), 8 October 2004 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Edited Manuscript (Folder 3 of 3), 8 October 2004 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Series 11: Feathers Brush My Heart 2, 1998-2013
  This series contains the material used to create the second volume of Feathers Brush My Heart. This includes letters from people whose stories are included within the volume.
  - Subseries 1: Research, 2002
    This subseries contains Browning’s plot notes concerning Feathers Brush My Heart 2.
    - Plot Notes, 2002, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 2: Correspondence, 1998-2013
    This subseries contains the letters relating to stories published within the volume, including publisher releases.
    - Publisher Releases, 2003-2008 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Story Submission, Anderson/Skull, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Story Submission, Bayer, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Story Submission, Bellini, circa 2013 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Story Submission, Bercot, 2003-2013 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Story Submission, Brand, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Story Submission, Brown, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Story Submission, Browning, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Story Submission, Brummer, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Story Submission, Bryant, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Story Submission, Burton, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Story Submission, Costa, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Story Submission, DiBella, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Story Submission, DiSalvo, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Story Submission, Edwards, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Story Submission, Freeland, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Story Submission, Gerhardt, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Story Submission, Harris, 2004-2013 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Story Submission, Hayden, 1998-2013 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Story Submission, Heuneman, 2003-2013 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Story Submission, Hoidahl, 2002-2013 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Story Submission, Holbrook, 2003-2013 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Story Submission, Horton, 1998-2013 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Story Submission, Illingworth, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Story Submission, Keffer, 2011-2013 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Story Submission, King, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Story Submission, Kirschbaum, 2011-2013 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Story Submission, Kowalk, 2002-2013 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Story Submission, Kupiec, 2002-2013 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Story Submission, Labie, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Story Submission, Lacey, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Story Submission, Lauria, 2003-2013 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Story Submission, Learn, 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Story Submission, Lee, 2003-2013 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Story Submission, Lilore, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Story Submission, Magafas, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Story Submission, Manka, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Story Submission, Margadonna, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Story Submission, Marshall, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Story Submission, Martakis, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Story Submission, Massio, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Story Submission, Mattson, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Story Submission, Maynard, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Story Submission, McCartney, 2003-2013 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Story Submission, McPhaden, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Story Submission, Mell, 2000, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 47)